<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Grow With Google | Learn Analytics For Free on Course Intern</title>
    <link>https://www.courseintern.com/tags/grow-with-google-learn-analytics-for-free/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Grow With Google | Learn Analytics For Free on Course Intern</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2008–2018, Steve Francia and the Admin; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 14:09:23 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.courseintern.com/tags/grow-with-google-learn-analytics-for-free/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Google Data Analytics Professional Certificate</title>
      <link>https://www.courseintern.com/post/google-courses/google-data-analytics-professional-certificate/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 14:09:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.courseintern.com/post/google-courses/google-data-analytics-professional-certificate/</guid>
      <description>
        
          &lt;h1 id=&#34;enriching-life-in-data-analytics&#34;&gt;Enriching Life in Data Analytics!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Data Analytics is the process of analyzing raw data so that we can pull out insights that are useful to companies.  If you want to mound your career and gain the job-ready skills you need to advance your career in Data Analytics. In this, there is no requirement for experience and provide 100% online learning under 10 hours of study a week. Nowadays there are in-demand jobs in the field of Data Analytics with a professional certificate from Google. You will be able to gain and understand the processes used by Data Analytics their day-to-day job. You will be able to understand how to get clear and organize data for analysis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;benefits-of-the-program&#34;&gt;Benefits of the program&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sharable certificate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;100% online courses&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Beginner level&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible Schedule&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;enrollment&#34;&gt;Enrollment:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can enroll in this program as its enrollment starts on 26 July 2021.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;professional-certificate&#34;&gt;Professional Certificate&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To boost your skills to start a new career,  Professional Certificate on Coursera helps you to become job-ready. Enroll in this program and you will get a 7-day free trial. You can pause and end your subscription at any time. You have to apply your skills with hands-on projects that manifest your job readiness to potential employers. To earn the certificate, you need to finish the project that you can share with your professional network. This may help you to kickstart your career in this program. Professional Certificate may also help you to prepare for the certification exam.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;there-are-8-courses-in-the-professional-certificate&#34;&gt;There are 8 Courses in the Professional Certificate&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Foundations: Data, Data, Everywhere&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ask Questions to Make Data-Driven Decisions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepare Data for Exploration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Process Data from Dirty to Clean&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyze Data to Answer Questions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Share Data Through the Art of Visualization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Data Analysis with R Programming&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;foundations-data-data-everywhere&#34;&gt;Foundations: Data, Data, Everywhere&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the course of the Google Data Analytics Certificate. In this course, you will be able to enhance your skills and will be able to bring into the world of data analytics with a hands-on curriculum developed by Google. In this course, you will be getting brief knowledge about key data analytics topics and data Analytics which improves their processes and identifies opportunities and trends. You will be getting knowledge about key analytical skills which include data cleaning, data analysis, data visualization.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;you-will-be-able-to&#34;&gt;You will be able to&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand the process of how Data Analytics do in their day-to-day job.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand the role of analytics in the Data ecosystem.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Explore job opportunities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand key analytical skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;ask-questions-to-make-data-driven-decisions&#34;&gt;Ask Questions to Make Data-Driven Decisions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the course in the Google Data Analytics Certificate. In this course, you will enhance the skills needed to apply to introductory-level data analyst jobs. You will be built-in with the topics that were introduced to you in the first course of the Google Data Analytics Certificate. You will be instruct and yield with hands-on ways to bring out common data analyst tasks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;you-will-be-able-to-1&#34;&gt;You will be able to&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn about basic techniques that can help in Data Analysis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Explore real-world business scenarios.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Help analysts to learn and understand problems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Give a better understanding of data-driven decision-making.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;prepare-data-for-exploration&#34;&gt;Prepare Data for Exploration&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this course, you will enhance the skills needed to apply to introductory-level data analyst jobs. You will be built-in with the topics that were introduced to you in the first and second course of the Google Data Analytics Certificate.  In this course, you will be introduced to new topics which will enhance practical data analytics skills. You will be instruct and yield with hands-on ways to bring out common data analyst tasks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;you-will-be-able-to-2&#34;&gt;You will be able to&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn best practices for organizing and securing data.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand how to access database and extract filter.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand some terms like structured and unstructured data.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand the importance of data ethics and data privacy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;process-data-from-dirty-to-clean&#34;&gt;Process Data from Dirty to Clean&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this course, you will enhance the skills needed to apply to introductory-level data analyst jobs. In this course, you will continue to build and understand data analytics. You will be also clear with the concepts and tools that data analysts use in their work. You will be exploring the “analyze” phase of the data analysis process. You will be instruct and yield with hands-on ways to bring out common data analyst tasks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;you-will-be-able-to-3&#34;&gt;You will be able to&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Check for data integrity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop basic SQL queries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Explore the elements of data cleaning reports.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand the results of cleaning data.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;analyze-data-to-answer-questions&#34;&gt;Analyze Data to Answer Questions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this course, you will enhance the skills needed to apply to introductory-level data analyst jobs. You will learn how to apply the analysis to make sense of the data you have collected. You will be able to learn how to use formulas, SQL queries, and functions. You will be enhancing your knowledge of how to solve complex calculations on your data. You will be instruct and yield with hands-on ways to bring out common data analyst tasks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;you-will-be-able-to-4&#34;&gt;You will be able to&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn how to organize data.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn how to complete calculations using SQL.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn the process for adjusting data.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand how to aggregate data in spreadsheets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;share-data-through-the-art-of-visualization&#34;&gt;Share Data Through the Art of Visualization&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the course in the Google Data Analytics Certificate. In this course, you will enhance the skills needed to apply to introductory-level data analyst jobs. In this course, you will learn how to visualize and present your data. You will be instruct and yield with hands-on ways to bring out common data analyst tasks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Scholars who complete this certificate program will be provided to apply as data analysts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;you-will-be-able-to-5&#34;&gt;You will be able to:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn the importance of data visualization.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand how to use Tableau to create the visualization.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand how to use Tableau to create dashboards.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Explore the principles involved with effective presentations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;data-analysis-with-r-programming&#34;&gt;Data Analysis with R Programming&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the course in the Google Data Analytics Certificate. In this course, you will enhance the skills needed to apply to introductory-level data analyst jobs. In this course, You’ll find out how to use RStudio.RStudio makes the environment that allows you to work with R.This also covers software applications and tools that are unique to R, such as the R package.
You will be instruct and yield with hands-on ways to bring out common data analyst tasks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Scholars who complete this certificate program will be provided to apply as data analysts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;you-will-be-able-to-6&#34;&gt;You will be able to&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn the benefits of the R programming language.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand how to use RStudio to apply R to your analysis.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn about R Markdown.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand the data frames and their uses in R.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;google-data-analytics-capstone-complete-a-case-study&#34;&gt;Google Data Analytics Capstone: Complete a Case Study&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the last and final course in the Google Data Analytics Certificate. In this course, you will enhance your skills and will provide you with opportunities to complete an optional case study, which will help prepare you for the data analytics job hunt. You will be instruct and yield with hands-on ways to bring out common data analyst tasks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Scholars who complete this certificate program will be provided to apply as data analysts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;you-will-be-able-to-7&#34;&gt;You will be able to&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn benefits and uses of case studies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Explore real-world business scenarios.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Examine different case study scenarios.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand how case studies can be a part of the job interview process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

        
      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
