<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Google Courses on Course Intern</title>
    <link>https://www.courseintern.com/categories/google-courses/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Google Courses on Course Intern</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2008–2018, Steve Francia and the Admin; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2021 14:00:37 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.courseintern.com/categories/google-courses/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Google Associate Android Developer Certification</title>
      <link>https://www.courseintern.com/post/google-courses/google-associate-android-developer-certification/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2021 14:00:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.courseintern.com/post/google-courses/google-associate-android-developer-certification/</guid>
      <description>
        
          &lt;h1 id=&#34;how-to-become-an-associate-android-developer&#34;&gt;HOW TO BECOME AN ASSOCIATE ANDROID DEVELOPER!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hey Folks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Associate Android Developer make your way towards mobile app development. You will be able to learn how to build simple Android apps in Kotlin training.  In this, there is no requirement for experience and provide 100% online learning under 10 hours of study a week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;benefits-of-the-program&#34;&gt;Benefits of the program&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sharable certificate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;100% online courses&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;android-basics-in-kotlin-courses&#34;&gt;Android Basics in Kotlin courses&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;unit-1-kotlin-basics&#34;&gt;Unit 1: Kotlin Basics&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;introduction-to-kotlin&#34;&gt;Introduction to Kotlin&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take your first step in the field of programming in Kotlin.In this, you need to add images and text to your android apps. You will be able to build your first Android app in Kotlin. Then you will be provided with a code lab where you will be provided with the short program in Kotlin using functions and loops to print a happy birthday message. After that, you will be provided a quiz which you need to answer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Create your first app: In this, you will create an app using Android Studio. Firstly you will be given an introduction to Android Studio. Then you need to download and install Android Studio. Then you will be able to create your first Android app. Then you will be able to run your app on your mobile device. After that, you will be provided a quiz which you need to answer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Build a basic layout: In this, you will be able to learn how to add images and text. You will be able to design a Birthday Card app. Then you will be able to add images to your Android app.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;unit-2-layouts&#34;&gt;Unit 2: Layouts&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this, you will be able to learn about layouts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;get-user-input-in-an-app-part-1&#34;&gt;Get user input in an app Part 1&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this you will be able to learn about two apps to advance your knowledge about UI layouts in Android. So firstly you will be given a bit description about tip calculator. After that, you will be able to learn new UI components,  such as editable text fields, radio buttons, and switches to build up the layout for your tip calculator app. You will be able to learn how to write Kotlin code to interact with the UI elements in the tip calculator app so that you can calculate. After that, you will be provided a quiz which you need to answer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;get-user-input-in-an-app-part-2&#34;&gt;Get user input in an app Part 2&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this, you can choose the color of your apps and apply them consistently throughout your app using themes. You will be able to change the launcher icon for your app. Then you can update your tip calculator app to look more professional and polished. After that, you will be provided a quiz which you need to answer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;display-a-scrollable-list&#34;&gt;Display a scrollable list&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Firstly you will be introduced to the Affirmations app and will be creating in this pathway. You will be able to learn how to create lists in Kotlin and loop through them. You will be introduced to RecycleView to display a scrollable list. You will be able to learn how to add images to the scrollable list.  After that, you will be provided a quiz which you need to answer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;unit-3navigation&#34;&gt;Unit 3:Navigation&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;navigate-between-screens&#34;&gt;Navigate between screens&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will be able to learn basic concepts of app navigation. You will be able to understand collections and how to manipulate them. You will be able to build a Words app with multiple activities. You will be able to learn about the activity lifecycle and different stages of an activity. At last, you need to test your knowledge to earn Navigate between screen badges.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;introduction-to-the-navigation-component&#34;&gt;Introduction to the Navigation component&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will be able to get an introduction to the Navigation component. You will be able to understand how to use fragments and implement navigation. You will be able to introduce MAD skills with the Navigation components.  At last, you need to test your knowledge to earn your Introduction to the Navigation component badge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Architecture components: Given a brief introduction about Unscramble app. You need to improve your app by implementing a ViewModel to retain app data. After that, you need to do the quiz for your knowledge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Advanced navigation app examples: You will be able to get an introduction to the Cupcake app which you will create in this pathway. You need to build a cupcake ordering app and use a shared ViewModel. Also, you need to manipulate the back stack in a custom way by modifying the cupcake apps so that the user can cancel the order.  At last, you need to test your knowledge to earn an Advanced Navigation app badge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;unit-4-connect-to-the-internet&#34;&gt;Unit 4: Connect to the Internet&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Coroutines: You will firstly be getting introduced to a Coroutines where you will learn to write clear code while building more complex and advanced apps. After that, you will be given a test for your knowledge and then you can earn your Coroutines badge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Get data from the internet: In this, you will be given an introduction to HTTP. You will be able to connect your app to the backend servers. You will learn about REST web services and will be able to load and display images using web URLs. After that, you will be given a test for your knowledge and earn your Get and display data from the internet badge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;unit-5-data-persistence&#34;&gt;Unit 5 :Data Persistence&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Introduction to SQL, Room, and Flow: In this, you will learn the basics of SQL, how to use and apply relational databases in an Android app. In this, you will learn the fundamentals of relational databases and will be able to practice running SQL queries. In this, you will be able to learn how to work with databases on Android. After that, you will be provided a quiz which you need to answer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Use Room for data persistence: In this, you will learn how to use and test Room Kotlin APIs. In this, you will be able to learn and build an app that uses the room to save inventory items into SQLS queries. You will be able to read, display, update and delete data from the app’s SQLite database using Room. After that, you will be provided a quiz which you need to answer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Cloud Career Readiness Program</title>
      <link>https://www.courseintern.com/post/google-courses/google-cloud-career-readiness-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2021 13:46:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.courseintern.com/post/google-courses/google-cloud-career-readiness-program/</guid>
      <description>
        
          &lt;h1 id=&#34;how-to-boost-your-google-cloud-skills&#34;&gt;How to Boost your Google Cloud Skills!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hey Folks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;intro&#34;&gt;Intro&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Google Cloud Career Readiness program is the 16-week on-demand program that has provided a path for students and faculty in higher education and helps you to prepare for a cloud-first workplace by making you ready for industry-recognized certifications. This program will help you to learn cloud computing fundamentals with hands-on practice in labs. With on-demand training on Coursera and Qwiklabs, you will build skills in topics related to cloud infrastructure, data analytics, and machine learning. The main objective of this program is to help the students to learn the essentials of the Google Cloud Platform and to explore this program. This program is very useful for the students who had a great dedication and willingness to explore their career in Google Cloud Program. This program is open for the students of all the Engineering streams of 3rd and 4th year, provided they should have high interest in making their career in Cloud Infrastructure. This program is specially designed to provide students with training, mentorship, and certification to launch their careers with companies seeking cloud talent. One should not pass over the chance to advance their career by learning  Google Cloud at your own pace, earning badges and certifications, and building projects. Google Cloud Career Readiness program is the journey to different certifications of Google Cloud. Google Cloud Career Readiness program offers provides the students to enhance their knowledge and career in this field. Career readiness programs develop logical reasoning skills to synthesize existing connections among various factors to solve problems. Apply for the career readiness program and help transform the future of the students. Google Cloud Career Readiness program leads the students to prepare them for future careers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;benefits&#34;&gt;Benefits&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Google Cloud Career Readiness program has the following benefits :&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This program provides students 100% Coursera.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This will provide 50% off on the ACE exam.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;significance&#34;&gt;Significance&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This program also has much significance as it identifies the caliber of the students as sometimes students at a younger age are often not aware of their true potential. This program creates opportunities that help them to analyze the current scenario of the job market. This program was quite unheard of until recent days. Critically analyzing the current market scope and skills possessed by the younger graduates, these programs are now given the utmost priority in every educational sector. A vision of future, career, Career Readiness Programs makes students industry-ready even before the completion of their graduation. Students nowadays never get a glimpse of the real-world waiting outside for them, but with thorough practice and determination, the students can polish their skills to make their future in Clouds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;who-can-facilitate-in-the-program&#34;&gt;Who can facilitate in the program&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this program, only teachers are eligible to Facilitate. If you are an interested student, please ask your professor to apply for it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;tracks&#34;&gt;Tracks&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This program offers an engaging platform for students to enhance their skills through two tracks: the Associate Cloud Engineer Track and the Data Analyst Track. If completed any one of the tracks then you can go for other tracks. The following are tracks of the Google Cloud Readiness Program.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The  Associate Cloud Engineer track.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Data Analyst Track&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The  Associate Cloud Engineer track is the 16-week track that provides students the opportunity to pursue their career in engineering and management roles related to cloud infrastructure, cloud-native application development, and data engineering. This track gives free access to architecting with Google Cloud platform specialization on Coursera which provides up to 40 hours of content...This on-demand training includes six-in depth courses with videos, hands-on labs, and quizzes. After completing the Specialization, students can earn the Architecting with Google compute engine Specialization certificate. Based on other completion timelines and other criteria, students receive a 50% discount on the certification exam whereas faculty receives a 100% discount. Associate Cloud Engineer develops applications, monitors operating, and manages enterprises solution. Associate Cloud Engineer exam assesses the ability to plan and configure a cloud solution. It ensures the successful operation of a cloud solution. It set up a cloud solution environment. It configures access and security. As you know that hands-on experience is crucial for success with the Associate Cloud Engineer Certification exam. In this, you will get credits to complete the labs on the Qwiklabs platform free of charge. This training will put you on the path to success for achieving the Associate Cloud Engineer track certification. This all will test your cloud skills.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;about-certification-exams&#34;&gt;About Certification Exams&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Certifications exam will be of 2 hours paper having registration fees of $125 (plus tax where applicable). The languages for this paper will be English, Japanese, Spanish. The format of these exams will be multiple choice questions and multi-select questions. The recommended experience should be 6 months + hands-on experience with Google Cloud.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After completing the certification exam, you will get access to digital badges and credentials which will help you to build your resume and unlock new job opportunities. Institutions around the world partnered with Google Cloud to solve student success.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;success-with-the-associate-cloud-engineer-track&#34;&gt;Success with the Associate Cloud Engineer track&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Operating systems and file systems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working with Linux at the command line and editing text files from the Linux command line.
-To participate in this track you will need a laptop or desktop with the latest versions of any popular web browser.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Google Chrome browser is recommended. An internet connection to access the Google Cloud Platform console is required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Data Analyst track is a 16-week track available for students who want to pursue their careers in data analytics, business intelligence, and management.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this track, students will get video-based training on Coursera and which will provide 30 hours of content in Google Cloud Platform Specialization. Students will get one benefit in doing this track as they will get free access to hands-on practice on labs. On completing the Specialization, students will be able to earn the from DATA to insights with this Google Cloud Platform Specialization certificate. To complete this Data Analyst track one should know well the ANSI SQLS and statistics.&lt;/p&gt;

        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Data Analytics Professional Certificate</title>
      <link>https://www.courseintern.com/post/google-courses/google-data-analytics-professional-certificate/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 14:09:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.courseintern.com/post/google-courses/google-data-analytics-professional-certificate/</guid>
      <description>
        
          &lt;h1 id=&#34;enriching-life-in-data-analytics&#34;&gt;Enriching Life in Data Analytics!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Data Analytics is the process of analyzing raw data so that we can pull out insights that are useful to companies.  If you want to mound your career and gain the job-ready skills you need to advance your career in Data Analytics. In this, there is no requirement for experience and provide 100% online learning under 10 hours of study a week. Nowadays there are in-demand jobs in the field of Data Analytics with a professional certificate from Google. You will be able to gain and understand the processes used by Data Analytics their day-to-day job. You will be able to understand how to get clear and organize data for analysis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;benefits-of-the-program&#34;&gt;Benefits of the program&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sharable certificate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;100% online courses&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Beginner level&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible Schedule&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;enrollment&#34;&gt;Enrollment:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can enroll in this program as its enrollment starts on 26 July 2021.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;professional-certificate&#34;&gt;Professional Certificate&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To boost your skills to start a new career,  Professional Certificate on Coursera helps you to become job-ready. Enroll in this program and you will get a 7-day free trial. You can pause and end your subscription at any time. You have to apply your skills with hands-on projects that manifest your job readiness to potential employers. To earn the certificate, you need to finish the project that you can share with your professional network. This may help you to kickstart your career in this program. Professional Certificate may also help you to prepare for the certification exam.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;there-are-8-courses-in-the-professional-certificate&#34;&gt;There are 8 Courses in the Professional Certificate&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Foundations: Data, Data, Everywhere&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ask Questions to Make Data-Driven Decisions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepare Data for Exploration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Process Data from Dirty to Clean&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyze Data to Answer Questions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Share Data Through the Art of Visualization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Data Analysis with R Programming&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;foundations-data-data-everywhere&#34;&gt;Foundations: Data, Data, Everywhere&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the course of the Google Data Analytics Certificate. In this course, you will be able to enhance your skills and will be able to bring into the world of data analytics with a hands-on curriculum developed by Google. In this course, you will be getting brief knowledge about key data analytics topics and data Analytics which improves their processes and identifies opportunities and trends. You will be getting knowledge about key analytical skills which include data cleaning, data analysis, data visualization.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;you-will-be-able-to&#34;&gt;You will be able to&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand the process of how Data Analytics do in their day-to-day job.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand the role of analytics in the Data ecosystem.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Explore job opportunities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand key analytical skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;ask-questions-to-make-data-driven-decisions&#34;&gt;Ask Questions to Make Data-Driven Decisions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the course in the Google Data Analytics Certificate. In this course, you will enhance the skills needed to apply to introductory-level data analyst jobs. You will be built-in with the topics that were introduced to you in the first course of the Google Data Analytics Certificate. You will be instruct and yield with hands-on ways to bring out common data analyst tasks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;you-will-be-able-to-1&#34;&gt;You will be able to&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn about basic techniques that can help in Data Analysis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Explore real-world business scenarios.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Help analysts to learn and understand problems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Give a better understanding of data-driven decision-making.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;prepare-data-for-exploration&#34;&gt;Prepare Data for Exploration&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this course, you will enhance the skills needed to apply to introductory-level data analyst jobs. You will be built-in with the topics that were introduced to you in the first and second course of the Google Data Analytics Certificate.  In this course, you will be introduced to new topics which will enhance practical data analytics skills. You will be instruct and yield with hands-on ways to bring out common data analyst tasks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;you-will-be-able-to-2&#34;&gt;You will be able to&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn best practices for organizing and securing data.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand how to access database and extract filter.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand some terms like structured and unstructured data.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand the importance of data ethics and data privacy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;process-data-from-dirty-to-clean&#34;&gt;Process Data from Dirty to Clean&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this course, you will enhance the skills needed to apply to introductory-level data analyst jobs. In this course, you will continue to build and understand data analytics. You will be also clear with the concepts and tools that data analysts use in their work. You will be exploring the “analyze” phase of the data analysis process. You will be instruct and yield with hands-on ways to bring out common data analyst tasks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;you-will-be-able-to-3&#34;&gt;You will be able to&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Check for data integrity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop basic SQL queries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Explore the elements of data cleaning reports.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand the results of cleaning data.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;analyze-data-to-answer-questions&#34;&gt;Analyze Data to Answer Questions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this course, you will enhance the skills needed to apply to introductory-level data analyst jobs. You will learn how to apply the analysis to make sense of the data you have collected. You will be able to learn how to use formulas, SQL queries, and functions. You will be enhancing your knowledge of how to solve complex calculations on your data. You will be instruct and yield with hands-on ways to bring out common data analyst tasks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;you-will-be-able-to-4&#34;&gt;You will be able to&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn how to organize data.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn how to complete calculations using SQL.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn the process for adjusting data.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand how to aggregate data in spreadsheets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;share-data-through-the-art-of-visualization&#34;&gt;Share Data Through the Art of Visualization&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the course in the Google Data Analytics Certificate. In this course, you will enhance the skills needed to apply to introductory-level data analyst jobs. In this course, you will learn how to visualize and present your data. You will be instruct and yield with hands-on ways to bring out common data analyst tasks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Scholars who complete this certificate program will be provided to apply as data analysts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;you-will-be-able-to-5&#34;&gt;You will be able to:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn the importance of data visualization.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand how to use Tableau to create the visualization.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand how to use Tableau to create dashboards.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Explore the principles involved with effective presentations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;data-analysis-with-r-programming&#34;&gt;Data Analysis with R Programming&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the course in the Google Data Analytics Certificate. In this course, you will enhance the skills needed to apply to introductory-level data analyst jobs. In this course, You’ll find out how to use RStudio.RStudio makes the environment that allows you to work with R.This also covers software applications and tools that are unique to R, such as the R package.
You will be instruct and yield with hands-on ways to bring out common data analyst tasks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Scholars who complete this certificate program will be provided to apply as data analysts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;you-will-be-able-to-6&#34;&gt;You will be able to&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn the benefits of the R programming language.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand how to use RStudio to apply R to your analysis.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn about R Markdown.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand the data frames and their uses in R.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;google-data-analytics-capstone-complete-a-case-study&#34;&gt;Google Data Analytics Capstone: Complete a Case Study&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the last and final course in the Google Data Analytics Certificate. In this course, you will enhance your skills and will provide you with opportunities to complete an optional case study, which will help prepare you for the data analytics job hunt. You will be instruct and yield with hands-on ways to bring out common data analyst tasks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Scholars who complete this certificate program will be provided to apply as data analysts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;you-will-be-able-to-7&#34;&gt;You will be able to&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn benefits and uses of case studies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Explore real-world business scenarios.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Examine different case study scenarios.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand how case studies can be a part of the job interview process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google UX Design Professional Certificate</title>
      <link>https://www.courseintern.com/post/google-courses/google-ux-design-professional-certificate/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 14:13:57 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.courseintern.com/post/google-courses/google-ux-design-professional-certificate/</guid>
      <description>
        
          &lt;h1 id=&#34;skillshare-in-ux-design&#34;&gt;Skillshare in UX design!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;intro&#34;&gt;Intro&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;UX design is the behavior and the patterns and habits of people to make their experience better. This is to your path to a career in UX Design. In this program, you will be able to learn in-demand skills. This program provides you with job-ready skills to start or advance your career. This will enhance your knowledge and gain an immersive understanding of practices in this field. This program doesn’t require any degree and experience. After enrolling in this program one can understand the basics of UX research like planning research studies, conducting interviews and usability studies, and synthesizing research results. This prepares you for a career in the high-growth field of UX design. UX designers focus on users’ interaction with products, like websites, apps, and physical objects.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-you-will-learn&#34;&gt;What you will learn&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will be able to follow the design process i.e empathize with users, define pain points, ideate solutions, create wireframes and prototypes, test and iterate on designs
You can easily apply foundational UX concepts, like user-centered design, accessibility, and equity-focused design.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;skills-you-will-gain&#34;&gt;Skills you will gain&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;User Experience (UX)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;UX Research&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;User Experience Design (UXD)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;UX design jobs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;enrollment&#34;&gt;Enrollment&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can enroll in this program as its enrollment starts on 9 July 2021&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;professional-certificate&#34;&gt;Professional Certificate&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To boost your skills to start a new career,  Professional Certificate on Coursera helps you to become job-ready. Enroll in this program and you will get a 7-day free trial. You can pause and end your subscription at any time. You have to apply your skills with hands-on projects that manifest your job readiness to potential employers. To earn the certificate, you need to finish the project that you can share with your professional network. This may help you to kickstart your career in this program. Professional Certificate may also help you to prepare for the certification exam.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;there-are-7-courses-in-the-professional-certificate&#34;&gt;There are 7 Courses in the Professional Certificate&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Foundations of User Experience (UX) Design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;UX design process: Empathize, Define, Ideate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build Wireframes and Low-Fidelity Prototypes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conduct UX Research and Test Early Concepts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create High-Fidelity Designs and Prototypes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsive Web Design in Adobe XD&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design a User Experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;foundations-of-user-experience-ux-design&#34;&gt;Foundations of User Experience (UX) Design&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Foundations of User Experience (UX) Design is the first of all the seven courses that will equip you with the skills and boost your career in this field. UX design focus on the interactions that people have with the product like websites, mobile apps, and physical objects.
This will help you to complete the hands-on activities related to the UX designer scenario. In this program, you can identify the factors that contribute to great user experience design. Scholars who complete the program should be appointed to apply for entry-level jobs as UX designers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;you-will-be-able-to&#34;&gt;You will be able to&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Define the field of UX and why it’s important.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Explore job opportunities and career paths&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in online UX communities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Why design sprints are important and useful?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;ux-design-process-empathize-define-ideate-ux-design-process&#34;&gt;UX design process: Empathize, Define, Ideate: UX design process&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Empathize, Define, Ideate is second in all seven courses that will enhance you with the skills needed to apply to entry-level jobs, and in this course, you will complete the first phase of the design process and this will help you to complete the hands-on activities related to the UX designer scenario. In this course; you can empathize with users to understand their needs and pain points. Scholars who complete the program should be appointed to apply for entry-level jobs as UX designers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;you-will-be-able-to-1&#34;&gt;You will be able to&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Common UX research methods.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conduct competitive audits.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Start designing a mobile app&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop problem statements to define user needs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;build-wireframes-and-low-fidelity-prototypes&#34;&gt;Build Wireframes and Low-Fidelity Prototypes&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This Is the third course that will provide you with the skills you need to apply to entry-level jobs in user experience (UX) design. In this, you will continue to design a mobile app. In this, you will be able to create storyboards and will be familiar with drawing too. You will be able to create paper wireframes and digital wireframes using the design tool Figma. Scholars who complete the program should be appointed to apply for entry-level jobs as UX designers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;you-will-be-able-to-2&#34;&gt;You will be able to:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop a goal statement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Apply the basics of drawing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design a low-fidelity prototype in Figma.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create two types of storyboards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;conduct-ux-research-and-test-early-concepts&#34;&gt;Conduct UX Research and Test Early Concepts&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This Is the fourth course that will provide you with the skills you need to apply to entry-level jobs in user experience (UX) design. In this course, you will be able to study and gather feedback about designs. Along with this, you will be able to modify your low-fidelity designs. This will help you to complete the hands-on activities related to the UX designer scenario.
Scholars who complete the program should be appointed to apply for entry-level jobs as UX designers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;you-will-be-able-to-3&#34;&gt;You will be able to&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Plan a UX research study,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create affinity diagrams for withdrawing the group and analyze data.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Modify low-fidelity designs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take notes during a usability study.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For certification, you need to complete the previous three courses or you need to have the ability to conduct user research to inform the creation of empathy maps, personas, user stories, user journey maps, and problem statements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;create-high-fidelity-designs-and-prototypes&#34;&gt;Create High-Fidelity Designs and Prototypes&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the fifth course that will provide  you with the skills you need to apply to entry-level jobs in user experience (UX) design. In this course, you need to follow the step-by-step tutorials to learn how to create high-fidelity designs. Afterward, you’ll be able to learn how to share your designs with development teams and highlight your work in your professional UX portfolio. t will help you to complete the hands-on activities related to the UX designer scenario.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Scholars who complete the program should be appointed to apply for entry-level jobs as UX designers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;you-will-be-able-to-4&#34;&gt;You will be able to&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Apply common visual design elements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exhibit how to design system can be organized.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build mockups and high-fidelity designs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Role of design critique sessions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A learner who has not completed the previous courses should have a complete understanding of the design process. This course is suitable for beginners who have completed the previous four courses of the Google UX Design Certificate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;responsive-web-design-in-adobe-xd&#34;&gt;Responsive Web Design in Adobe XD&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Responsive Web Design in Adobe XD is the sixth course that will equip you with the skills you need to apply to entry-level jobs in user experience (UX) design.
It will help you to complete the hands-on activities related to the UX designer scenario.
Scholars who complete the program should be appointed to apply for entry-level jobs as UX designers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;you-will-be-able-to-5&#34;&gt;You will be able to&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with design systems in Adobe XD.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Apply common layouts for web pages.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Concern about the UX design process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create or update a UX-focused resume&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A learner who has not completed the previous courses should have a complete understanding of the design process. This course is suitable for beginners who have completed the previous four courses of the Google UX Design Certificate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;design-a-user-experience&#34;&gt;Design a User Experience&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Design a User Experience is the last course that will enhance you with the skills you need to apply to entry-level jobs in user experience (UX) design. In this course, you will design a dedicated mobile app and a responsive website too. It will help you to complete the hands-on activities related to the UX designer scenario.
Scholars who complete the program should be appointed to apply for entry-level jobs as UX designers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;you-will-be-able-to-6&#34;&gt;You will be able to&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Define each step of the UX design process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interview for an entry-level UX design job.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepare you for job applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build wireframes and mockups.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Project Management Professional Certificate</title>
      <link>https://www.courseintern.com/post/google-courses/google-project-management-professional-certificate/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 13:50:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.courseintern.com/post/google-courses/google-project-management-professional-certificate/</guid>
      <description>
        
          &lt;h1 id=&#34;training-to-be-the-best&#34;&gt;Training to be the best!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hey Folks, read on more to find out about Google project management professional certificate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;intro&#34;&gt;Intro&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Project Management is the application of knowledge, skills, tools, and techniques to meet the project requirements and achieve the desired outcome. In this course, you will learn how to hone the skills to become a truly great project manager and the awesome thing about project management is that it spans a lot of industries and company types as it doesn’t require deep technical knowledge.
Google Project Management certificate provides you with job-ready skills to start or advance your career in project management and get access to practice exercises, quizzes, discussion forums job search help, and more on Coursera. This will enhance your knowledge and gain an immersive understanding of practices in this field. You can also build your new career in the high-growth field of project management. In this, you don’t need any experience as well as a degree.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-you-will-learn&#34;&gt;What you will learn&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn how to make effective project documentation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Practice problem-solving, strategic communication, and stakeholder management through real-world scenarios.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;enrollment&#34;&gt;Enrollment&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can enroll in this program as its enrollment starts on 2 July 2021&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;professional-certificate&#34;&gt;Professional Certificate&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To boost your skills to start a new career,  Professional Certificate on Coursera helps you to become job-ready. Enroll in this program and you will get a 7-day free trial. You can pause and end your subscription at any time. You have to apply your skills with hands-on projects that manifest your job readiness to potential employers. To earn the certificate you need to finish the project which you can share with your professional network as well. This may help you to kickstart your career in this program. Professional Certificate may also help you to prepare for the certification exam.
There are 6 Courses in the Professional Certificate:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;foundation-of-project-management&#34;&gt;Foundation of project management&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This course is the first in the series of six courses that may accoutre you all with the skills that you need to apply to the introductory-level roles in project management. The Project manager plays an important role in leading planning and facilitates the critical project to help the organization succeed. In this course, you will be able to gain a deeper understanding of the role and responsibilities of a project manager. You may also familiarize the kinds of jobs that you can pursue after the completion of the program. Scholars who complete the program should be appointed to apply for introductory-level jobs as project managers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;you-will-be-able-to&#34;&gt;You will be able to:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Define and explore project management roles and responsibilities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Grab skills on how to become a successful project manager.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Define change management and the role of the project manager in this process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Acknowledge organizational structure and culture and its impact.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;project-initiation&#34;&gt;Project Initiation:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Starting a Successful Project: This is the second course in the series of six courses of the Google Project Management Certificate program. This course will show how to set up a project for success in the first phase of the project. In this course, you will grab how to define and manage project goals, deliverables, scope, and success criteria. Project managers will guide you and provide you with hands-on approaches for accomplishing these tasks. They will show you the best project management tools and resources for the job at hand. Scholars who complete the program should be appointed to apply for introductory-level jobs as project managers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;you-will-be-able-to-1&#34;&gt;You will be able to&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Determine the project&#39;s benefits and costs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Complete a stakeholder analysis&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Define project goals and deliverables.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand the key components of the project initiate phase.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;project-planning&#34;&gt;Project Planning&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Putting it all together: This is the third course in the series of  Google Project Management Certificate programs. In this course; you will explore how to map out a project in the second phase of the project. You will be able to grab how to build and manage a budget. In this, you will grab how to draft and manage communication plans and you will also be able to acknowledge how to organize project documentation. The project manager will instruct and provide you with hands-on approaches for completing these tasks. Scholars who complete the program should be appointed to apply for introductory-level jobs as project managers. In this course, no previous experience is required.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;you-will-be-able-to-2&#34;&gt;You will be able to&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Explain why milestones are important.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Explain why the project plan is necessary.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Describe how to manage and maintain a budget.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identifies tools and best practices to build a project plan.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;project-execution-running-the-project&#34;&gt;Project Execution: Running the Project&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the fourth course out of the six series of the  Google Project Management Certificate program. In this course; you will explore the closing phase of the project life cycle. You will learn how to manage, communicate changes and risks. You will also examine how to compute data, how to use data to inform your decision-making, and how to effectively present that data. The project manager will instruct and provide you with hands-on approaches for completing these tasks.
Scholars who complete the program should be appointed to apply for introductory-level jobs as project managers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;you-will-be-able-to-3&#34;&gt;You will be able to&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Explain the purpose of retrospective.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Describe the closing process of stakeholders.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrate how to analyze the data.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Compare the different tracking methods.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;agile-project-management&#34;&gt;Agile Project Management&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the fifth course in the series of the six  Google Project Management Certificate programs. This course will explore the history and philosophy of Agile project management. In this, you will learn about Syrum. You will learn about exploring its pillars also. You will also be able to grab how to search for and land opportunities in Agile roles. The project manager will instruct and provide you with hands-on approaches for completing these tasks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Scholars who complete the program should be appointed to apply for introductory-level jobs as project managers. In this course, no previous experience is required.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;you-will-be-able-to-4&#34;&gt;You will be able to&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Explain the pillars of Syrum.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implement Agile’s value-driven delivery strategies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Guide a job search for an Agile role&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build and manage a Product Backlog&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;capstone-applying-project-management-in-the-real-world&#34;&gt;Capstone: Applying Project Management in the Real World&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the last course in the Google Project Management Certificate program. In this final course, you will practice applying project management knowledge and skills. To start with this course learners should complete Course 1-5 as they provided the foundation necessary to complete the activities in this course. After completing this course one can apply to apply for introductory-level jobs as a project manager. In this course, you have the opportunity to claim a certification of completion badge that will be recognizable to employers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;you-will-be-able-to-5&#34;&gt;You will be able to&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop  a portfolio of project management artifacts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage stakeholders and teams.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Organize plans, and communicate project details.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepare for the  interview for project management jobs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google IT Support Professional Certificate</title>
      <link>https://www.courseintern.com/post/google-courses/google-it-support-professional-certificate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 14:06:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.courseintern.com/post/google-courses/google-it-support-professional-certificate/</guid>
      <description>
        
          &lt;h1 id=&#34;get-more-out-of-now&#34;&gt;Get more out of now!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IT support is for the students who want to build their career in IT and they will be able to gain the skills required to succeed in an entry-level IT capacity. Nowadays there are in-demand jobs in the field of IT with a professional certificate from Google. In this, there is no requirement for experience and provide 100% online learning under 10 hours of study a week. If you want to mound your career and gain the job-ready skills you need to advance your career in the IT field&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;find-the-programs-available&#34;&gt;FIND THE PROGRAMS AVAILABLE&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Launch a new career in IT&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advance your IT career&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;launch-a-new-career-in-it&#34;&gt;Launch a new career in IT&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Google IT Support Professional Certificate&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this, you need to Prepare for an entry-level role in IT support by earning the Google IT Support Professional Certificate. No experience is required to get started. In an IT career, you need to design to take you from beginner to job-ready in under six months. You need to complete hands-on practice to help them to make their career in this field.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;how-to-enroll&#34;&gt;How to enroll&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Google IT Support Professional Certificate&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This will path your career in the IT field and you will become job-ready in less than 6 months. In this, you will learn how to provide end-to-end customer support, ranging from identifying problems to troubleshooting and debugging. You will be able to learn to perform day-to-day IT support tasks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;benefits-of-the-program&#34;&gt;Benefits of the program&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sharable certificate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;100% online courses&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Beginner level&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;enrollment&#34;&gt;Enrollment&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can enroll in this program as its enrollment starts on 17 July 2021.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;professional-certificate&#34;&gt;Professional Certificate&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To boost your skills to start a new career,  Professional Certificate on Coursera helps you to become job-ready. Enroll in this program and you will get a 7-day free trial. You can pause and end your subscription at any time. You have to apply your skills with hands-on projects that manifest your job readiness to potential employers. To earn the certificate, you need to finish the project that you can share with your professional network. This may help you to kickstart your career in this program. Professional Certificate may also help you to prepare for the certification exam.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;there-are-5-courses-in-the-professional-certificate&#34;&gt;There are 5 Courses in the Professional Certificate&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Technical Support Fundamentals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Bits and Bytes of Computer Networking&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Operating Systems and You: Becoming a Power User&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;System Administration and IT Infrastructure Services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;IT Security: Defense against the digital dark arts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;technical-support-fundamentals&#34;&gt;Technical Support Fundamentals&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Technical Support Fundamentals is the first course that aims to prepare you for a role as an entry-level IT Support Specialist. In this course, you will be able to learn different facts about IT like computer hardware, the Internet, and computer software.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;you-will-be-able-to&#34;&gt;You will be able to&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand how the binary system works.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand what the Internet is.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand how applications are created and how it works.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Utilize soft skills in an Information Technology setting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;the-bits-and-bytes-of-computer-networking&#34;&gt;The Bits and Bytes of Computer Networking&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Bits and Bytes of Computer Networking is the second course to provide a full overview of computer networking. In this course, you will be able to learn how to describe computer networks in terms of a five-layer model.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;you-will-be-able-to-1&#34;&gt;You will be able to&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;understand cloud computing and cloud storage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;learn network services like DNS and DHCP&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;understand all of the standard protocols&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn the fundamentals of modern networking technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;operating-systems-and-you-becoming-a-power-user&#34;&gt;Operating Systems and You: Becoming a Power User&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is the third course that will provide hands-on practice. In this course, you will learn the main components of an operating system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;you-will-be-able-to-2&#34;&gt;You will be able to&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Performing tasks like managing software and users.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Install and remove software on the Windows and Linux operating systems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand how system processes work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand how to manage the system.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;system-administration-and-it-infrastructure-services&#34;&gt;System Administration and IT Infrastructure Services&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;System Administration and IT Infrastructure Services is the fourth course that will work on a single computer to an entire fleet. In this course, you will learn how to manage and configure servers. You will also learn about how to recover the organization&#39;s IT infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;you-will-be-able-to-3&#34;&gt;You will be able to&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage the tools that your organization will use&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand how to manage infrastructure servers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Practices for selecting services for the organization.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage an organization’s computers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;it-security-defense-against-the-digital-dark-arts&#34;&gt;IT Security: Defense against the digital dark arts&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is the last course that covers a wide variety of IT security concepts, tools, and best practices. In this course, you will cover network security solutions, ranging from firewalls to Wifi encryption options. There are three As of information security: authentication, authorization, and accounting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;you-will-be-able-to-4&#34;&gt;You will be able to&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Difference between authentication and authorization.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Get Best practices for securing a network.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn Various authentication systems and types.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Grab how to grasp security concepts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;advance-your-it-career&#34;&gt;Advance your IT career&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this, you will be able to learn  Python Programming and explore how to apply it in the IT field. You will be able to practice your technical skills with hands-on projects and assessments. You need to prepare for a variety of opportunities in IT. In this you will be able to learn tasks by writing a Python script. You will be able to manage IT resources at scale, both for physical machines and virtual machines in the cloud. You will be able to learn how to use Git and GitHub.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;There are 6 Courses in the Professional Certificate&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Crash Course on Python&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Using Python to interact with the Operating System&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Introduction to Git and Github&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Troubleshooting and Debugging Techniques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Configuration Management and the Cloud&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Automating Real-World Tasks with Python&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;crash-course-on-python&#34;&gt;Crash Course on Python&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is the course that will teach you how to write simple programs in python using the most common structure. You will be able to learn the benefits of programming in IT roles. Along with that, you will be able to get hands-on experience with programming concepts through interactive exercises and real-life examples.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;using-python-to-interact-with-the-operating-system&#34;&gt;Using Python to interact with the Operating System&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is the course in which you will be able to manipulate files and processes on your computer’s operating system. You will practice using the Linux command line on a virtual machine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;introduction-to-git-and-github&#34;&gt;Introduction to Git and Github&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this course, you will be able to get about Git, how to keep track of the different versions of your code. You will be able to reserve your code&#39;s history in Git and get together with others in GitHub.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;troubleshooting-and-debugging-techniques&#34;&gt;Troubleshooting and Debugging Techniques&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this course, you will be solving real-life problems that you might come across in your IT role. You will be getting problems that can affect any operating system. You will be looking into technical problems and see how to apply them to solve different real-world scenarios.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;configuration-management-and-the-cloud&#34;&gt;Configuration Management and the Cloud&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this course, you will be given a brief how-to apply automation to manage fleets of computers. You will also read some new terms like configuration management, which means the automation technique, that lets you manage the configuration of our computers at scale. You will also learn how to use Puppet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;automating-real-world-tasks-with-python&#34;&gt;Automating Real-World Tasks with Python&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will learn all the concepts you have learned until now in this course. You will be acknowledged about Qwiklabs that will challenge you to use multiple skills at once. You will be able to describe a problem and use those skills to create a solution. At last, you will be given a project in which you need to describe what your customer needs, and you need to create a program to do it!&lt;/p&gt;

        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Cloud Ready Facilitator Program</title>
      <link>https://www.courseintern.com/post/google-courses/google-cloud-ready-facilitator-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Mar 2021 13:26:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.courseintern.com/post/google-courses/google-cloud-ready-facilitator-program/</guid>
      <description>
        
          &lt;h1 id=&#34;google-cloud-ready-facilitator-program-revealed&#34;&gt;Google Cloud Ready Facilitator Program Revealed!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hey Folks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Google Cloud Ready Facilitator Program is the program that provides all the opportunities to start up your career in the Google Cloud Platform. In this program, Google officially provides you all hands-on practice on Qwiklabs for the Google Cloud Platform. While doing this program you can grab and practice many concepts of computing, application development, big data, and machine learning. This program offers students a job-ready curriculum. This program will allow students to earn industry-recognized credentials. This program will reward the participants with free Google goodies, Google badges, Google Cloud certification, and free access to Google programs based on milestones achieved by the participants by completing quests and skill badges. If you get stuck while doing some quest and skill badges then our facilitators will always be available to help you out. Students who want to enhance their knowledge and skills in the field of Google Cloud Platform can unite in this program. This program helps the students to train them in industry-ready cloud skills and enhance their skills while participating in such programs. Students who want to become experts in Google Cloud and want to enhance their skills can participate in this program. Manifest your cloud skills by earning exclusive badges for your resume. To solve real-world problems Skill badges are shareable credentials that recognize your ability to solve real-world problems with your cloud knowledge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;eligibility-criteria-to-enroll-in-the-program&#34;&gt;Eligibility criteria to enroll in the program:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working internet.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Laptop with latest chrome browser.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Age criteria should be 18+&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enroll in higher educational program in India.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To enroll in this program, the main thing to remember is that this program has a timeline from 10 April 2021 to 10 June 2021. You all can enroll in this program whether you are a fresher or an experienced person. The last date to fill the form is on 9th April till 11:59 PM. The form will require you to:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fill in personal and academic details with the size of the T-shirt.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Submit the link to Qwiklabs Public profile.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Go to the page and get the URL of your profile.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After filling the form you will get a confirmation on your g-mail. If you don&#39;t get the confirmation mail then wait for 15-30 min as well as check your spam box. If any participant needs to change any information in the form then they may reach out to the Facilitator and they may help them out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once you fill the form you will get a confirmation email with some instructions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The instructions to avail of FREE credits pass on Qwiklabs. You need credits to take labs on Qwiklabs that are part of the program.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What&#39;s the last date of the program?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The timelines of the program.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What&#39;s the last date to get a chance at those rewards?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Other program-related information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you still didn&#39;t receive the confirmation mail then you must have provided the wrong Qwiklab profile URL above. If the link provided to you is not working in the enrolment email you can simply copy-paste the hardcoded URL in your browser beside each link in the mail and that should work too. If you don’t receive an invitation email after applying through the enrollment form then you may talk to the Facilitator. They may help you to enroll in the program.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This program has been divided into four milestones and individually milestones have their different prices.
To earn the prizes in this program you have to complete the milestones.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-higher-the-milestones-the-higher-the-prizes&#34;&gt;&amp;quot;THE HIGHER THE MILESTONES, THE HIGHER THE PRIZES&amp;quot;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-milestones-are&#34;&gt;The milestones are&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Milestone 1 -- To achieve milestone1 you need to complete any 8
quests and 4 skill badges in the program. As the reward for completing
milestone1, you will be getting one google cloud t-shirt, Google cloud badge, Google cloud Pen, and Google cloud stickers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Milestone 2 --  To achieve milestone2 you need to complete any 16
quests and 8 skill badges in the program. As the reward for completing
milestone2, you will be getting one sling bag, a Google cloud t-shirt, a Google Cloud badge, Google cloud Pen, and Google cloud stickers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Milestone3 -- To achieve milestone3 you need to complete any 24
quests and 12 skill badges in the program, As the reward for completing the milestone3 you will be getting one bag, sling bag, Google cloud t-shirt, Google cloud badge, Google cloud Pen, and Google cloud stickers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Milestone4 -- To achieve milestone4 you need to complete any 30 quests and 15 skill badges in the program, As the reward for completing the milestone4 you will be getting all the rewards of milestone1 to
milestone3  but along with that you will be able to get free access to the Google Cloud Career Readiness program. You can get to learn more about this program” &lt;a href=&#34;https://events.withgoogle.com/googlecloudready-facilitator-program/#content&#34;&gt;https://events.withgoogle.com/googlecloudready-facilitator-program/#content&lt;/a&gt;”.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember that you can receive the prizes only for the milestone achieved and not for the ones before that. If you complete any of the above-mentioned Milestone of the program prizes will be
delivered to you within two months after the completion of the program to your own residential address.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If any participant has already received schwag in any of the Google Cloud Program like 30 days of Google Program 2020 will not be eligible to get prizes if they had completed any of the milestones. If you want to receive the prizes you need to complete the quest and skill badges after the enrollment period. Remember if you had completed it before it wouldn’t be counted. If you want you need to make a new account on Qwiklabs with a new email ID.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You might be thinking what is the difference between Quests and Skill badges. Quests have many training labs whereas skill badges it has training labs and a challenge lab too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;for-better-convenience-they-have-divided-tracks-into-3-parts&#34;&gt;For better convenience, they have divided tracks into 3 parts.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cloud Infrastructure Track - In Cloud Infrastructure Track you need to finish out any 10 quests and 8 skill badges in this track.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cloud-native Application Development Track - In Cloud-native Application Development Track you need to utter any 10 quests and 3 skill badges in this track.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Big Data &amp;amp; Machine Learning Track - In Big Data &amp;amp; Machine Learning you need to finalize any 10 quests and 3 skill badges in this track.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

        
      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
