<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Coursera google IT support professional certificate on Course Intern</title>
    <link>https://www.courseintern.com/tags/coursera-google-it-support-professional-certificate/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Coursera google IT support professional certificate on Course Intern</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2008–2018, Steve Francia and the Admin; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 14:06:05 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.courseintern.com/tags/coursera-google-it-support-professional-certificate/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Google IT Support Professional Certificate</title>
      <link>https://www.courseintern.com/post/google-courses/google-it-support-professional-certificate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 14:06:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.courseintern.com/post/google-courses/google-it-support-professional-certificate/</guid>
      <description>
        
          &lt;h1 id=&#34;get-more-out-of-now&#34;&gt;Get more out of now!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IT support is for the students who want to build their career in IT and they will be able to gain the skills required to succeed in an entry-level IT capacity. Nowadays there are in-demand jobs in the field of IT with a professional certificate from Google. In this, there is no requirement for experience and provide 100% online learning under 10 hours of study a week. If you want to mound your career and gain the job-ready skills you need to advance your career in the IT field&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;find-the-programs-available&#34;&gt;FIND THE PROGRAMS AVAILABLE&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Launch a new career in IT&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advance your IT career&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;launch-a-new-career-in-it&#34;&gt;Launch a new career in IT&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Google IT Support Professional Certificate&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this, you need to Prepare for an entry-level role in IT support by earning the Google IT Support Professional Certificate. No experience is required to get started. In an IT career, you need to design to take you from beginner to job-ready in under six months. You need to complete hands-on practice to help them to make their career in this field.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;how-to-enroll&#34;&gt;How to enroll&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Google IT Support Professional Certificate&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This will path your career in the IT field and you will become job-ready in less than 6 months. In this, you will learn how to provide end-to-end customer support, ranging from identifying problems to troubleshooting and debugging. You will be able to learn to perform day-to-day IT support tasks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;benefits-of-the-program&#34;&gt;Benefits of the program&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sharable certificate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;100% online courses&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Beginner level&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;enrollment&#34;&gt;Enrollment&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can enroll in this program as its enrollment starts on 17 July 2021.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;professional-certificate&#34;&gt;Professional Certificate&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To boost your skills to start a new career,  Professional Certificate on Coursera helps you to become job-ready. Enroll in this program and you will get a 7-day free trial. You can pause and end your subscription at any time. You have to apply your skills with hands-on projects that manifest your job readiness to potential employers. To earn the certificate, you need to finish the project that you can share with your professional network. This may help you to kickstart your career in this program. Professional Certificate may also help you to prepare for the certification exam.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;there-are-5-courses-in-the-professional-certificate&#34;&gt;There are 5 Courses in the Professional Certificate&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Technical Support Fundamentals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Bits and Bytes of Computer Networking&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Operating Systems and You: Becoming a Power User&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;System Administration and IT Infrastructure Services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;IT Security: Defense against the digital dark arts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;technical-support-fundamentals&#34;&gt;Technical Support Fundamentals&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Technical Support Fundamentals is the first course that aims to prepare you for a role as an entry-level IT Support Specialist. In this course, you will be able to learn different facts about IT like computer hardware, the Internet, and computer software.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;you-will-be-able-to&#34;&gt;You will be able to&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand how the binary system works.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand what the Internet is.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand how applications are created and how it works.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Utilize soft skills in an Information Technology setting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;the-bits-and-bytes-of-computer-networking&#34;&gt;The Bits and Bytes of Computer Networking&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Bits and Bytes of Computer Networking is the second course to provide a full overview of computer networking. In this course, you will be able to learn how to describe computer networks in terms of a five-layer model.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;you-will-be-able-to-1&#34;&gt;You will be able to&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;understand cloud computing and cloud storage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;learn network services like DNS and DHCP&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;understand all of the standard protocols&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn the fundamentals of modern networking technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;operating-systems-and-you-becoming-a-power-user&#34;&gt;Operating Systems and You: Becoming a Power User&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is the third course that will provide hands-on practice. In this course, you will learn the main components of an operating system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;you-will-be-able-to-2&#34;&gt;You will be able to&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Performing tasks like managing software and users.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Install and remove software on the Windows and Linux operating systems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand how system processes work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand how to manage the system.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;system-administration-and-it-infrastructure-services&#34;&gt;System Administration and IT Infrastructure Services&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;System Administration and IT Infrastructure Services is the fourth course that will work on a single computer to an entire fleet. In this course, you will learn how to manage and configure servers. You will also learn about how to recover the organization&#39;s IT infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;you-will-be-able-to-3&#34;&gt;You will be able to&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage the tools that your organization will use&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand how to manage infrastructure servers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Practices for selecting services for the organization.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage an organization’s computers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;it-security-defense-against-the-digital-dark-arts&#34;&gt;IT Security: Defense against the digital dark arts&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is the last course that covers a wide variety of IT security concepts, tools, and best practices. In this course, you will cover network security solutions, ranging from firewalls to Wifi encryption options. There are three As of information security: authentication, authorization, and accounting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;you-will-be-able-to-4&#34;&gt;You will be able to&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Difference between authentication and authorization.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Get Best practices for securing a network.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn Various authentication systems and types.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Grab how to grasp security concepts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;advance-your-it-career&#34;&gt;Advance your IT career&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this, you will be able to learn  Python Programming and explore how to apply it in the IT field. You will be able to practice your technical skills with hands-on projects and assessments. You need to prepare for a variety of opportunities in IT. In this you will be able to learn tasks by writing a Python script. You will be able to manage IT resources at scale, both for physical machines and virtual machines in the cloud. You will be able to learn how to use Git and GitHub.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;There are 6 Courses in the Professional Certificate&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Crash Course on Python&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Using Python to interact with the Operating System&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Introduction to Git and Github&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Troubleshooting and Debugging Techniques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Configuration Management and the Cloud&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Automating Real-World Tasks with Python&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;crash-course-on-python&#34;&gt;Crash Course on Python&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is the course that will teach you how to write simple programs in python using the most common structure. You will be able to learn the benefits of programming in IT roles. Along with that, you will be able to get hands-on experience with programming concepts through interactive exercises and real-life examples.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;using-python-to-interact-with-the-operating-system&#34;&gt;Using Python to interact with the Operating System&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is the course in which you will be able to manipulate files and processes on your computer’s operating system. You will practice using the Linux command line on a virtual machine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;introduction-to-git-and-github&#34;&gt;Introduction to Git and Github&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this course, you will be able to get about Git, how to keep track of the different versions of your code. You will be able to reserve your code&#39;s history in Git and get together with others in GitHub.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;troubleshooting-and-debugging-techniques&#34;&gt;Troubleshooting and Debugging Techniques&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this course, you will be solving real-life problems that you might come across in your IT role. You will be getting problems that can affect any operating system. You will be looking into technical problems and see how to apply them to solve different real-world scenarios.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;configuration-management-and-the-cloud&#34;&gt;Configuration Management and the Cloud&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this course, you will be given a brief how-to apply automation to manage fleets of computers. You will also read some new terms like configuration management, which means the automation technique, that lets you manage the configuration of our computers at scale. You will also learn how to use Puppet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;automating-real-world-tasks-with-python&#34;&gt;Automating Real-World Tasks with Python&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will learn all the concepts you have learned until now in this course. You will be acknowledged about Qwiklabs that will challenge you to use multiple skills at once. You will be able to describe a problem and use those skills to create a solution. At last, you will be given a project in which you need to describe what your customer needs, and you need to create a program to do it!&lt;/p&gt;

        
      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
