<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>google cloud career readiness program on Course Intern</title>
    <link>https://www.courseintern.com/tags/google-cloud-career-readiness-program/</link>
    <description>Recent content in google cloud career readiness program on Course Intern</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2008–2018, Steve Francia and the Admin; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2021 13:46:02 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.courseintern.com/tags/google-cloud-career-readiness-program/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Google Cloud Career Readiness Program</title>
      <link>https://www.courseintern.com/post/google-courses/google-cloud-career-readiness-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2021 13:46:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.courseintern.com/post/google-courses/google-cloud-career-readiness-program/</guid>
      <description>
        
          &lt;h1 id=&#34;how-to-boost-your-google-cloud-skills&#34;&gt;How to Boost your Google Cloud Skills!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hey Folks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;intro&#34;&gt;Intro&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Google Cloud Career Readiness program is the 16-week on-demand program that has provided a path for students and faculty in higher education and helps you to prepare for a cloud-first workplace by making you ready for industry-recognized certifications. This program will help you to learn cloud computing fundamentals with hands-on practice in labs. With on-demand training on Coursera and Qwiklabs, you will build skills in topics related to cloud infrastructure, data analytics, and machine learning. The main objective of this program is to help the students to learn the essentials of the Google Cloud Platform and to explore this program. This program is very useful for the students who had a great dedication and willingness to explore their career in Google Cloud Program. This program is open for the students of all the Engineering streams of 3rd and 4th year, provided they should have high interest in making their career in Cloud Infrastructure. This program is specially designed to provide students with training, mentorship, and certification to launch their careers with companies seeking cloud talent. One should not pass over the chance to advance their career by learning  Google Cloud at your own pace, earning badges and certifications, and building projects. Google Cloud Career Readiness program is the journey to different certifications of Google Cloud. Google Cloud Career Readiness program offers provides the students to enhance their knowledge and career in this field. Career readiness programs develop logical reasoning skills to synthesize existing connections among various factors to solve problems. Apply for the career readiness program and help transform the future of the students. Google Cloud Career Readiness program leads the students to prepare them for future careers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;benefits&#34;&gt;Benefits&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Google Cloud Career Readiness program has the following benefits :&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This program provides students 100% Coursera.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This will provide 50% off on the ACE exam.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;significance&#34;&gt;Significance&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This program also has much significance as it identifies the caliber of the students as sometimes students at a younger age are often not aware of their true potential. This program creates opportunities that help them to analyze the current scenario of the job market. This program was quite unheard of until recent days. Critically analyzing the current market scope and skills possessed by the younger graduates, these programs are now given the utmost priority in every educational sector. A vision of future, career, Career Readiness Programs makes students industry-ready even before the completion of their graduation. Students nowadays never get a glimpse of the real-world waiting outside for them, but with thorough practice and determination, the students can polish their skills to make their future in Clouds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;who-can-facilitate-in-the-program&#34;&gt;Who can facilitate in the program&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this program, only teachers are eligible to Facilitate. If you are an interested student, please ask your professor to apply for it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;tracks&#34;&gt;Tracks&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This program offers an engaging platform for students to enhance their skills through two tracks: the Associate Cloud Engineer Track and the Data Analyst Track. If completed any one of the tracks then you can go for other tracks. The following are tracks of the Google Cloud Readiness Program.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The  Associate Cloud Engineer track.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Data Analyst Track&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The  Associate Cloud Engineer track is the 16-week track that provides students the opportunity to pursue their career in engineering and management roles related to cloud infrastructure, cloud-native application development, and data engineering. This track gives free access to architecting with Google Cloud platform specialization on Coursera which provides up to 40 hours of content...This on-demand training includes six-in depth courses with videos, hands-on labs, and quizzes. After completing the Specialization, students can earn the Architecting with Google compute engine Specialization certificate. Based on other completion timelines and other criteria, students receive a 50% discount on the certification exam whereas faculty receives a 100% discount. Associate Cloud Engineer develops applications, monitors operating, and manages enterprises solution. Associate Cloud Engineer exam assesses the ability to plan and configure a cloud solution. It ensures the successful operation of a cloud solution. It set up a cloud solution environment. It configures access and security. As you know that hands-on experience is crucial for success with the Associate Cloud Engineer Certification exam. In this, you will get credits to complete the labs on the Qwiklabs platform free of charge. This training will put you on the path to success for achieving the Associate Cloud Engineer track certification. This all will test your cloud skills.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;about-certification-exams&#34;&gt;About Certification Exams&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Certifications exam will be of 2 hours paper having registration fees of $125 (plus tax where applicable). The languages for this paper will be English, Japanese, Spanish. The format of these exams will be multiple choice questions and multi-select questions. The recommended experience should be 6 months + hands-on experience with Google Cloud.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After completing the certification exam, you will get access to digital badges and credentials which will help you to build your resume and unlock new job opportunities. Institutions around the world partnered with Google Cloud to solve student success.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;success-with-the-associate-cloud-engineer-track&#34;&gt;Success with the Associate Cloud Engineer track&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Operating systems and file systems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working with Linux at the command line and editing text files from the Linux command line.
-To participate in this track you will need a laptop or desktop with the latest versions of any popular web browser.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Google Chrome browser is recommended. An internet connection to access the Google Cloud Platform console is required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Data Analyst track is a 16-week track available for students who want to pursue their careers in data analytics, business intelligence, and management.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this track, students will get video-based training on Coursera and which will provide 30 hours of content in Google Cloud Platform Specialization. Students will get one benefit in doing this track as they will get free access to hands-on practice on labs. On completing the Specialization, students will be able to earn the from DATA to insights with this Google Cloud Platform Specialization certificate. To complete this Data Analyst track one should know well the ANSI SQLS and statistics.&lt;/p&gt;

        
      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
