<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Google Project Management Professional Certificate on Course Intern</title>
    <link>https://www.courseintern.com/tags/google-project-management-professional-certificate/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Google Project Management Professional Certificate on Course Intern</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2008–2018, Steve Francia and the Admin; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 13:50:44 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.courseintern.com/tags/google-project-management-professional-certificate/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Google Project Management Professional Certificate</title>
      <link>https://www.courseintern.com/post/google-courses/google-project-management-professional-certificate/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 13:50:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.courseintern.com/post/google-courses/google-project-management-professional-certificate/</guid>
      <description>
        
          &lt;h1 id=&#34;training-to-be-the-best&#34;&gt;Training to be the best!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hey Folks, read on more to find out about Google project management professional certificate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;intro&#34;&gt;Intro&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Project Management is the application of knowledge, skills, tools, and techniques to meet the project requirements and achieve the desired outcome. In this course, you will learn how to hone the skills to become a truly great project manager and the awesome thing about project management is that it spans a lot of industries and company types as it doesn’t require deep technical knowledge.
Google Project Management certificate provides you with job-ready skills to start or advance your career in project management and get access to practice exercises, quizzes, discussion forums job search help, and more on Coursera. This will enhance your knowledge and gain an immersive understanding of practices in this field. You can also build your new career in the high-growth field of project management. In this, you don’t need any experience as well as a degree.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-you-will-learn&#34;&gt;What you will learn&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn how to make effective project documentation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Practice problem-solving, strategic communication, and stakeholder management through real-world scenarios.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;enrollment&#34;&gt;Enrollment&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can enroll in this program as its enrollment starts on 2 July 2021&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;professional-certificate&#34;&gt;Professional Certificate&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To boost your skills to start a new career,  Professional Certificate on Coursera helps you to become job-ready. Enroll in this program and you will get a 7-day free trial. You can pause and end your subscription at any time. You have to apply your skills with hands-on projects that manifest your job readiness to potential employers. To earn the certificate you need to finish the project which you can share with your professional network as well. This may help you to kickstart your career in this program. Professional Certificate may also help you to prepare for the certification exam.
There are 6 Courses in the Professional Certificate:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;foundation-of-project-management&#34;&gt;Foundation of project management&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This course is the first in the series of six courses that may accoutre you all with the skills that you need to apply to the introductory-level roles in project management. The Project manager plays an important role in leading planning and facilitates the critical project to help the organization succeed. In this course, you will be able to gain a deeper understanding of the role and responsibilities of a project manager. You may also familiarize the kinds of jobs that you can pursue after the completion of the program. Scholars who complete the program should be appointed to apply for introductory-level jobs as project managers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;you-will-be-able-to&#34;&gt;You will be able to:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Define and explore project management roles and responsibilities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Grab skills on how to become a successful project manager.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Define change management and the role of the project manager in this process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Acknowledge organizational structure and culture and its impact.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;project-initiation&#34;&gt;Project Initiation:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Starting a Successful Project: This is the second course in the series of six courses of the Google Project Management Certificate program. This course will show how to set up a project for success in the first phase of the project. In this course, you will grab how to define and manage project goals, deliverables, scope, and success criteria. Project managers will guide you and provide you with hands-on approaches for accomplishing these tasks. They will show you the best project management tools and resources for the job at hand. Scholars who complete the program should be appointed to apply for introductory-level jobs as project managers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;you-will-be-able-to-1&#34;&gt;You will be able to&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Determine the project&#39;s benefits and costs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Complete a stakeholder analysis&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Define project goals and deliverables.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand the key components of the project initiate phase.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;project-planning&#34;&gt;Project Planning&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Putting it all together: This is the third course in the series of  Google Project Management Certificate programs. In this course; you will explore how to map out a project in the second phase of the project. You will be able to grab how to build and manage a budget. In this, you will grab how to draft and manage communication plans and you will also be able to acknowledge how to organize project documentation. The project manager will instruct and provide you with hands-on approaches for completing these tasks. Scholars who complete the program should be appointed to apply for introductory-level jobs as project managers. In this course, no previous experience is required.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;you-will-be-able-to-2&#34;&gt;You will be able to&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Explain why milestones are important.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Explain why the project plan is necessary.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Describe how to manage and maintain a budget.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identifies tools and best practices to build a project plan.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;project-execution-running-the-project&#34;&gt;Project Execution: Running the Project&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the fourth course out of the six series of the  Google Project Management Certificate program. In this course; you will explore the closing phase of the project life cycle. You will learn how to manage, communicate changes and risks. You will also examine how to compute data, how to use data to inform your decision-making, and how to effectively present that data. The project manager will instruct and provide you with hands-on approaches for completing these tasks.
Scholars who complete the program should be appointed to apply for introductory-level jobs as project managers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;you-will-be-able-to-3&#34;&gt;You will be able to&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Explain the purpose of retrospective.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Describe the closing process of stakeholders.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrate how to analyze the data.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Compare the different tracking methods.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;agile-project-management&#34;&gt;Agile Project Management&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the fifth course in the series of the six  Google Project Management Certificate programs. This course will explore the history and philosophy of Agile project management. In this, you will learn about Syrum. You will learn about exploring its pillars also. You will also be able to grab how to search for and land opportunities in Agile roles. The project manager will instruct and provide you with hands-on approaches for completing these tasks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Scholars who complete the program should be appointed to apply for introductory-level jobs as project managers. In this course, no previous experience is required.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;you-will-be-able-to-4&#34;&gt;You will be able to&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Explain the pillars of Syrum.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implement Agile’s value-driven delivery strategies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Guide a job search for an Agile role&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build and manage a Product Backlog&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;capstone-applying-project-management-in-the-real-world&#34;&gt;Capstone: Applying Project Management in the Real World&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the last course in the Google Project Management Certificate program. In this final course, you will practice applying project management knowledge and skills. To start with this course learners should complete Course 1-5 as they provided the foundation necessary to complete the activities in this course. After completing this course one can apply to apply for introductory-level jobs as a project manager. In this course, you have the opportunity to claim a certification of completion badge that will be recognizable to employers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;you-will-be-able-to-5&#34;&gt;You will be able to&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop  a portfolio of project management artifacts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage stakeholders and teams.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Organize plans, and communicate project details.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepare for the  interview for project management jobs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

        
      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
